<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Reviews>
    <Review>
        <Title>Hollow Knight</Title>
        <Image>Images/Hollow_Knight.png</Image>
        <Description>Hollow Knight is a 2D action-adventure game with an emphasis on traditional 2D
            animation and skillful gameplay. Journey to Hallownest, a vast and ancient underground
            kingdom inhabited by a bizarre collection of insects and monsters. Players will forge
            their own path as they explore ruined cities, forests of fungus, temples of bone and
            other fantastic lands, all on their way to uncovering an ancient mystery.</Description>
        <Platforms>PC Wii U Nintendo Switch PlayStation 4 Xbox One</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2018-07-12</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Team Cherry</Developer>
        <Publisher>Team Cherry</Publisher>
        <Genres>Metroidvania</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>90</Score>
            <Score>9.1</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>Batman: Arkham Knight</Title>
        <Image>Images/Batman_Arkham_Knight.png</Image>
        <Description>Batman confronts the ultimate threat against the city he has been sworn to
            protect. The Scarecrow returns to congeal an imposing array of super villains, including
            The Penguin, Two-Face and Harley Quinn, to summarily destroy The Dark Knight. The game
            introduces Rocksteady's uniquely-designed imagining of the Batmobile drivable for the
            first time in the franchise. Batman: Arkham Knight offers gamers a complete Batman
            experience as they rip through the streets and soar across the skyline of the iconic
            Gotham City.</Description>
        <Platforms>PlayStation 4 Xbox One PC Nintendo Switch</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2015-06-23</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Rocksteady Studios</Developer>
        <Publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment</Publisher>
        <Genres>Open-World Action</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>87</Score>
            <Score>8.1</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>DiRT Rally 2.0</Title>
        <Image>Images/Dirt_Rally_2.0.jpg</Image>
        <Description>DiRT Rally 2.0 dares you to carve your way through a selection of iconic rally
            locations from across the globe, in the most powerful off-road vehicles ever made,
            knowing that the smallest mistake could end your stage. You will need to rely on your
            instincts with the most immersive and truly focused off-road experience yet, including a
            new authentic handling model, tyre choice and surface deformation. Power your rally car
            through real-life off-road environments in New Zealand, Argentina, Spain, Poland,
            Australia and the USA, with only your co-driver and instincts to guide you. Race on
            eight official circuits from the FIA World Rallycross championship, complete with
            licensed Supercars and support series. Develop your team and cars around race
            strategies, and progress through a varied selection of Events and Championships in both
            a single player Career Campaign and a competitive online environment.</Description>
        <Platforms>PlayStation 4 PC Xbox One</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2019-02-26</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Codemasters</Developer>
        <Publisher>Codemasters</Publisher>
        <Genres>Auto Racing Sim</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>84</Score>
            <Score>6.3</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>Wolfenstein: The New Order</Title>
        <Image>Images/Wolfenstein_The_New_Order.jpg</Image>
        <Description>1946: Europe. World War II rages on across Europe. Where the Allies once
            pressed advantage, the Nazi forces have turned the tide in dramatic fashion behind the
            technologically advanced war machine of General Wilhelm Strasse, aka Deathshead. When a
            final Allied assault on Deathshead's compound fails, the Allies’ greatest hope falls
            with it. 1960: Europe. The war is over. And the Nazis are triumphant victors. Using
            unrelenting force and brutal intimidation, the Nazis have brought even the most powerful
            nations to their knees. The Nazi regime now rules the globe with an iron fist. You are
            Captain B.J. Blazkowicz, the American War Hero. After delving into this world of
            darkness, you must launch an impossible counter-offensive against the monstrous Nazi
            regime. Only you dare stand up against an unstoppable army of Nazi robots and hulking
            Super Soldiers. Only you can stop Deathshead. Only you can rewrite history.</Description>
        <Platforms>PlayStation 3 PC Xbox 360 PlayStation 4 Xbox One</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2014-05-20</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>MachineGames</Developer>
        <Publisher>Bethesda Softworks</Publisher>
        <Genres>FPS</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>79</Score>
            <Score>8.1</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>Titanfall 2</Title>
        <Image>Images/Titanfall_2.jpg</Image>
        <Description>In single player, Titanfall 2 delivers a crafted experience that explores the
            unique bond between man and machine. Playable offline, the single player campaign in
            Titanfall 2 lets fans step out onto The Frontier as a Militia rifleman with aspirations
            of becoming an elite Pilot. Stranded behind enemy lines and facing overwhelming odds,
            players must team up with a veteran Titan to uphold a mission they were never meant to
            carry out. In multiplayer, Respawn is continuing to evolve their gameplay to provide a
            more robust experience that delivers expanded depth and variety that includes six new
            Titans, deeper Pilot abilities, more customization options, and a robust progression
            system that is sure to satisfy fans.</Description>
        <Platforms>Xbox One PC PlayStation 4</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2016-10-28</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Respawn Entertainment</Developer>
        <Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
        <Genres>FPS</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>89</Score>
            <Score>8.6</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>Assassin's Creed IV: Black Flag</Title>
        <Image>Images/ACBF.png</Image>
        <Description>The year is 1715. Pirates rule the waters of the Caribbean and have established
            a lawless Republic. Among these outlaws is a lethal young captain named Edward Kenway.
            His notorious exploits earn the respect of legends like Blackbeard, but draw him into an
            ancient war that may destroy everything the pirates have built for themselves.</Description>
        <Platforms>PlayStation 4 Xbox 360 PC Wii U PlayStation 3 Xbox One</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2013-10-29</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Ubisoft</Developer>
        <Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
        <Genres>Open-World Action</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>88</Score>
            <Score>8.2</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>Cuphead</Title>
        <Image>Images/Cuphead.png</Image>
        <Description>Cuphead is a classic run and gun action game primarily focused on boss battles.
            Inspired by the cartoons of the 1930s, the visuals and audio are carefully created with
            the same techniques of the era, i.e. traditional cel animation (hand drawn &amp; hand
            inked), watercolor backgrounds, and original jazz recordings. Play as Cuphead or Mugman
            (in single player or co-op) as you traverse strange worlds, acquire new weapons, learn
            powerful super moves, and discover hidden secrets.</Description>
        <Platforms>Xbox One PC Nintendo Switch PlayStation 4</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2017-09-29</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Studio MDHR</Developer>
        <Publisher>Studio MDHR</Publisher>
        <Genres>2D Platformer</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>86</Score>
            <Score>8.5</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
    <Review>
        <Title>The Messenger</Title>
        <Image>Images/The_Messenger.png</Image>
        <Description>As a demon army besieges his village, a young ninja ventures through a cursed
            world, to deliver a scroll paramount to his clan's survival. What begins as a classic
            action platformer soon unravels into an expansive time-traveling adventure full of
            thrills, surprises, and humor.</Description>
        <Platforms>PC PlayStation 4 Xbox One Nintendo Switch</Platforms>
        <ReleaseDate>2018-08-30</ReleaseDate>
        <Developer>Sabotage Studio</Developer>
        <Publisher>Devolver Digital</Publisher>
        <Genres>Metroidvania</Genres>
        <Scores>
            <Score>86</Score>
            <Score>8.4</Score>
        </Scores>
    </Review>
</Reviews>

<!-- <Review>
    <Title></Title>
    <Image>Images/</Image>
    <Description></Description>
    <Platforms></Platforms>
    <ReleaseDate></ReleaseDate>
    <Developer></Developer>
    <Publisher></Publisher>
    <Genres></Genres>
    <Scores>
        <Score></Score>
        <Score></Score>
    </Scores>
</Review> -->